Register of the Charles Easton Rothwell papers, 1924-1995
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings, 1939-1983 (Box 10-21)
  - "The United Nations and World Peace in the Second Decade: Toward a More Effective Organization," speech, Institute of World Affairs, typescript outline, 1955 December 11-14 (Box-folder 18: 8)
    Includes agenda, brochures, and correspondence.
  - "New Europe in a New World," speech, U.S. Naval Postgraduate School, Monterey, California, holograph and typescript outline, 1956 January 18 (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - "A New Europe in a New World," speech, Chicago Alumni Conference, typescript, 1956 March 3 (Box-folder 18: 10)
  - "Europe - Arena of Conflict or Crucible of Peace," holograph outline for a speech, 1956 May 19 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - "A New Europe in a New World," excerpts from talk, Stanford Alumni Conference, Stanford University, Caifornia, typescript, 1956 May 19 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - "With Windows Upon the Past and a Door to the Future," speech, Friends of the Library, University of Oregon, holograph and typescript outline, 1956 May 26 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - "The Position of the United States in the International Political System," U.S. Naval Postgraduate School, Monterey, California, typescript outline for a speech, 1957 April 17 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - "The Meaning and the Price of Peace," Sixteenth Stanford Business Conference, Stanford University, California, typescript, 1957 July 22-25 (Box-folder 18: 15)
    Includes brochure, printed conference proceedings, typescript outline, related correspondence, and telegram.
  - "United Europe - Progress - Pitfalls," speech, World Affairs Council, Monterey, California, typescript outline, 1957 September 27 (Box-folder 18: 16)
    Includes clippings and related correspondence.
  - "Secret Russian Documents and Free Public Knowledge," speech, luncheon meeting, Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce and Kiwanis Club, Palo Alto, California, typescript outline, 1957 November 21 (Box-folder 18: 17)
    Includes correspondence and newsletter.
  - "Political Integration and Disintegration: Methods in Interdisciplinary Research," speech, University of San Francisco, California, holograph outline, 1957 December 27-28 (Box-folder 18: 18)
  - "Secret Russian Documents and Free Public Knowledge," speech, Phoenix, Arizona, typescript outline and text of a speech, 1958 January 19 (Box-folder 18: 19)
  - "The Hoover Institution in the Post-Sputnik Era," speech, Santa Barbara, California, typescript, 1958 January 22 (Box-folder 18: 20)
    The same speech was to be delivered at the Oakland Rotary Club in April of 1958.
  - "The Politics of Peace," speech, Eugene, Oregon, holograph outline, 1958 February 21 (Box-folder 18: 21)
  - "Satellites, Security, and Sense," speech, Western Association of College and University Business Offices, Highlands Inn, Carmel, California, typescript outline, 1958 April 24 (Box-folder 18: 22)
    Includes correspondence, memoranda, and program.
  - "The Dilemma of the 1958 Graduate," commencement address, Santa Rosa Center, California, typescript, 1958 June 6 (Box-folder 18: 23)
  - "Minds, Mazes, and Missions," commencement address, Portland State College, typescript, 1958 June 15 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Remarks, dedication of the Henry F. Grady Room, World Affairs Council of Northern California, typescript, 1958 July 10 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - "The United Nations-1958," speech, United Nations Week, typescript, 1958 October 20 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Typescript chapters of an untitled book relating to Soviet policy and activities, typescript, 1958 December (Box-folder 19: 4)
  - Speech, Mills Quarterly, printed copy, 1959 February (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - "The Role of the Learned Society Today," California Historical Society Quarterly, printed copy, 1959 March (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - "The Achievement of Excellence," speech, Pacific Northwest Conference on Higher Education, Ashland, Oregon, typescript, 1959 July 27 (Box-folder 19: 7)
    Also delivered at the American Association of University Women, Walnut Creek Branch, California, 1960 February 17?
  - Address, Mills College, Mills Stream, printed copy, 1959 July 6 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - "Education: The Arrow and the Idea," convocation address, Mills Concert Hall, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1959 September 23 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - "The Lamp Burns with a Cleaner Flame," inaugural address, Mills College, Oakland, California, Mills Quarterly, printed copy, 1959 October 8 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - "College Affairs," speech, Mills Assembly, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript outline, 1959 December 9 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - "Peace and Goodwill: 1959," speech, Oakland Kiwanis Club, ?, typescript outline, 1959 December 12 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - "An Academic Achievement," speech, Mills Assembly, Mills College, Oakland, California, Mills Quarterly, printed copy, 1960 January 6 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - "The Power of Education in Human Relations," speech, symposium for Business and Industrial Executives, St. Mary's College, typescript, 1960 February 3 (Box-folder 19: 14)
  - "College Events," Mills Assembly, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1960 February 10 (Box-folder 19: 15)
  - "The College Beyond the Looking Glass," address as President-Elect, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1960? February 25 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - "Where Principles Count," speech, Panel of Americans, St. Francis Hotel, San Francisco, California, holograph outline, 1960 March 17 (Box-folder 19: 17)
  - "Educating for Excellence," speech, Commonwealth Club, San Francisco, California, typescript, 1960 March 25 (Box-folder 19: 18)
  - "What the Next Decade Holds for the Private College," speech to be delivered, Southern California Conference, Mills College Alumnae Association, Huntington-Sheraton Hotel, Pasadena, California, typescript, 1960 May 7 (Box-folder 19: 19)
    Includes press release.
  - "You Shall Behold Creation," sermon, faculty service, Chapel of Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1960 May 15 (Box-folder 19: 20)
  - "Moonshots and Green Baize," speech, Bank of America Awards Luncheon, typescript, 1960 May 20 (Box-folder 19: 21)
  - Commencement speech to seniors, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1960 June 5 (Box-folder 19: 22)
  - "What Kind of Star," remarks, Alumnae Husband Dinner, Mills College, Oakland, California, holograph and typescript outline, 1960 June 10 (Box-folder 19: 23)
  - "The Cultivated Person," address, convocation, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1960 September 28 (Box-folder 19: 24)
  - "The Creation of the United Nations Charter," speech, Edith M. Coulter Lecture, California Library Association, Pasadena, California, typescript, 1960 October 6 (Box-folder 19: 25)
  - "The Meaning of Excellence in Education," paper, Oklahoma City, Chamber of Commerce, Oklahoma, typescript, 1961 January 20 (Box-folder 19: 26)
  - Message on women's education, CBS telecast, to be taped at KPIX Studios, San Francisco, California, typescript, 1961 March 29 (Box-folder 19: 27)
  - "The Poor Megalopolite," speech, Goucher Alumnae Clubs, typescript outline, 1961 April 17 (Box-folder 19: 28)
  - "The Commonwealth of Learning," address, University of California Chapter, Phi Beta Kappa, typescript, 1961 May 22 (Box-folder 19: 29)
  - "The Commonwealth of Learning," commencement address, Golden Gate College Graduating Class, Veterans War Memorial Building, San Francisco, California, typescript, 1961 June 13 (Box-folder 19: 30)
    Includes programs.
  - Speech on Civil War, Bohemian Grove, typescript, 1961 July 23 (Box-folder 19: 31)
  - "The World of Learning," convocation address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1961 September 27 (Box-folder 19: 32)
  - "From High School, To College: New Problems in Adaptation in the High School Curriculum," speech, Reed College, Portland, Oregon, typescript, 1961 September 28 (Box-folder 19: 33)
  - "The Price of Peace," speech, Pan American Medical Association, typescript, 1961 December 2 (Box-folder 19: 34)
  - Commencement address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1962 (Box-folder 19: 35)
  - "Some Views to Travel With," speech, San Francisco, California, typescript, 1962 February 14 (Box-folder 19: 36)
  - "Is the Foreign Student Exchange Program a Success?," speech, typescript outline, 1962 February 28 (Box-folder 19: 37)
  - "The Future of the United Nations," speech, World Affairs Council, Peacock Court, Hotel Mark Hopkins, San Francisco, California, typescript outline, 1962 March 24 (Box-folder 19: 38)
  - "Springtime in Bohemia," speech, typescript, 1962 April 19 (Box-folder 19: 39)
  - "How Long Does Achievement Last?," speech, typescript outline, 1962 May 3 (Box-folder 19: 40)
  - Remarks, senior breakfast, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1962 June 8 (Box-folder 19: 41)
  - "Sierra Myth and Magic," Bohemian Grove, typescript, 1962 July 15 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Introductory remarks, dinner in honor of William Lister Rogers, Peacock Court and Room of the Dons, Hotel Mark Hopkins, San Francisco, typescript, 1962 September 26 (Box-folder 20: 2)
    Includes related correspondence and invitation.
  - "Turn the Telescope Around," convocation address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1962 September 26 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - "100 Years of Education," Hundredth Anniversary Dinner Address, Centennial of Sarah Dix Hamlin School, Gold Room, Fairmont Hotel, San Francisco, typescript, 1962 October 10 (Box-folder 20: 4)
    Includes correspondence and invitation.
  - "Aspirations, Expectations, and the Educated Woman," speech, typescript, 1962 December (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - "Pattern for the Future," Woman's Education, printed copy, 1962 December (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - "Commencement 1963," address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - "Pine Top Picnic," remarks, typescript, 1963 June 6 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Remarks, alumnae family dinner, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1963 June 8 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - "Where Does the Road Lead?," convocation address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1963 September 25 (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - "The Community College and Liberal Learning," Founders Day, Bakersfield College, California, typescript, 1963 October 22 (Box-folder 20: 11)
  - Address, Founders Day, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1963 October 30 (Box-folder 20: 12)
  - Article, part I, second draft, Committee on College and World Affairs, typescript, 1963 November 7 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Speech, Mills College ceremonies attending the death of President John F. Kennedy, typescript, 1963 November 22 (Box-folder 20: 14)
    Includes correspondence and printed matter.
  - "Liberal Learning in a Changing World," typescript, 1963 December 12 (Box-folder 20: 15)
    Includes "President's Letter," 1964 January, and Summary of Conclusions, undated.
  - "Commencement 1964," address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - "Liberal Learning in a Changing World," University and College Leaders' Conference, Education and World Affairs, Del Monte Lodge, Pebble Beach, California, typescript, 1964 January (Box-folder 20: 17)
    Includes related correspondence, holograph notes, list of participants, statistics, tentative agenda, and typescript report. Also includes a revised copy, 1964 January 28.
  - Speech, Education of Women and the Role of Women, San Francisco College for Women, Lone Mountain, San Francisco, typescript outline, 1964 March 14 (Box-folder 20: 18)
  - Statement, Coordinating Council on Higher Education, State Scholarship Assistance and Its Impact on California Higher Education, Particularly in the Independent Colleges and Universities, typescript, 1964 March 31 (Box-folder 20: 19)
  - "The Reaffirmation of Liberal Education," address, nineteenth National Conference on Higher Education, typescript, 1964 April 20 (Box-folder 20: 20)
  - "How to Live in a New Kind of World," speech, Monterey Institute for Foreign Study, Monterey, California, typescript outline, 1964 June (Box-folder 20: 21)
  - Remarks, senior breakfast, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript outline, 1964 June 5 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - "Shakespeare in Our Lives," speech, Bohemian Grove, San Francisco, California, typescript outline, 1964 July 30 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - "The Mills College We Must Have," Kaiser dinner speech, Mills College Program, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1964 October 23 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - Founders Day address, typescript, 1964 October 24 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - "The Paradox of Freedom," speech, California State College, Hayward, California, typescript, 1964 November 18 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - "Thankagiving at Bohemia," address, typescript, 1964 November 19 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - "Honolulu," speech, holograph outline, 1964 December 29 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - "Commencement 1965," address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Address, alumnae luncheon, typescript outline, 1965 June 4 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Speech, senior breakfast, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1965 June 4 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Address, alumnae dinner, typescript, 1965 June 5 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Speech, Baccalaureate, typescript, 1965 June 6 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - "The Delightfully Uncommon Woman," Association of American University Women, Portland, Oregon, typescript, 1965 June 22 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    Includes printed copy, Association of American University Women Journal, 1966 January.
  - "1965 - Year of International Cooperation," speech, Zonta International, typescript, 1965 July 9 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - "Changing Colleges," convocation address, typescript, 1965 September 29 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - "Dedication of Lucie Stern Hall," remarks, typescript, 1965 October 29 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Founders Day address, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1965 October 29 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - "Grist For a New Mills," Founders Day speech, Claremont Country Club, typescript, 1965 October 29 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - "The Year of the Student," comments on his speech, Seven College Council Christmas Showcase, Claremont Hotel, San Francisco, California?, typescript, 1965 November 15 (Box-folder 21: 19)
  - "The World in Higher Education," remarks, Education and World Affairs Conference, Los Angeles, California, typescript outline with holograph notes, 1966 January 28 (Box-folder 21: 20)
  - Welcoming remarks, Western College Association Annual Meeting, Hotel Claremont, California, typescript, 1966 March 10-11 (Box-folder 21: 21)
    Includes related correspondence, program, report, and schedule.
  - Remarks, unveiling of a portrait of Warren Olney, Warren Olney Hall, typescript, 1966 April 14 (Box-folder 21: 22)
  - "Heralds and Prophets," commencement address, College of Holy Names, Oakland, California, typescript, 1966 May 22 (Box-folder 21: 23)
  - Speech, Kaiser dinner for major gift prospects, Kaiser Center, typescript outline, 1966 May 24 (Box-folder 21: 24)
  - Speech, dedication, Isabella Cowell Health Center, typescript, 1966 June 10 (Box-folder 21: 25)
    Includes printed program.
  - Remarks, senior breakfast, typescript, 1966 June 10 (Box-folder 21: 26)
  - "Strategy For World Law," speech, Symposium for Peace, College of Notre Dame, Belmont, California, typescript, 1966 July 16 (Box-folder 21: 27)
    Includes related announcement, correspondence, and tentative program.
  - "Looking Glass Reflections," convocation address, typescript, 1966 September 28 (Box-folder 21: 28)
  - Remarks, alumnae council greeting, Reinhardt House, typescript outline, 1966 October 24 (Box-folder 21: 29)
  - Speech, Convocation Founders Day, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1966 October 28 (Box-folder 21: 30)
  - Remarks, chapel dedication, Mills College, Oakland, California, typescript, 1967 June 11 (Box-folder 21: 31)
  - Address, Convocation Founders Day, typescript, 1968 October 28 (Box-folder 21: 32)
  - "Woodside," typescript, 1968 (Box-folder 21: 33)
    Includes a copy with commentaries.
  - "Woodside," typescript, 1970 (Box-folder 21: 34)
  - "Mills College Education in Some World Perspectives," Cyrus and Susan Mills Society, typescript, 1970 May 21 (Box-folder 21: 35)
  - Statement, the President's Commission for the United Nations, San Francisco hearings, typescript, 1971 January 12 (Box-folder 21: 36)
  - "Revolutionary Common Sense," speech, Bohemian Grove, typescript, 1975 July 22 (Box-folder 21: 37)
  - "What Should We Worry About in Asia," speech, Palo Alto Rotary Club, Palo Alto, California, typescript outline, 1979 March 5 (Box-folder 21: 38)
  - Oral history project - United Nations, interview, Inverness, California, typescript, 1983 March 24 (Box-folder 21: 39)
    Includes a letter related to the project.
- Stanford University and Hoover Institution, 1932-1988 (Box 22-27)
  Brochures, bulletins, clippings, correspondence, colloquium, faculty records, financial records, memoranda, minutes of meetings, newsletters, printed matter, reports, schedule, telegrams, and travel information relating to the years of Charles Rothwell's service to Stanford University and the Hoover Institution, arranged alphabetically by physical form. Also includes the materials from various conferences and seminars he participated in at Stanford, California, and in Cambridge, England. See also: General Subject File and United Nations and State Department series.
  - General (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Brochure (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Bulletin (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - By-Laws and Rules of Order as contained in the Trustees Manual (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Clippings (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Box-folder 22: 6)
    - 1933 April-November (Box-folder 22: 7)
    - 1937 November (Box-folder 22: 8)
    - 1939 February-May (Box-folder 22: 9)
    - 1940 November (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - 1941 March (Box-folder 22: 11)
    - 1946
      - July (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - September-December (Box-folder 22: 13)
    - 1947
      - January (Box-folder 22: 14)
      - February-April (Box-folder 22: 15)
      - May-July (Box-folder 22: 16)
      - December (Box-folder 22: 17)
    - 1948 January-November (Box-folder 22: 18)
    - 1949 January-November (Box-folder 22: 19)
    - 1951
      - February-May (Box-folder 22: 20)
      - June-July (Box-folder 22: 21)
      - August-October (Box-folder 22: 22)
    - 1952 March-November (Box-folder 22: 23)
    - 1953 January-November (Box-folder 22: 24)
    - 1954 January-August (Box-folder 22: 25)
    - 1955 January-April (Box-folder 22: 26)
    - 1956 March-December (Box-folder 22: 27)
    - 1957 June-October (Box-folder 22: 28)
    - 1958 March-December (Box-folder 22: 29)
    - 1959
      - January (Box-folder 22: 30)
      - February-April (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - 1961 February (Box-folder 23: 2)
    - 1970 April (Box-folder 23: 3)
    - 1976 November (Box-folder 23: 4)
    - 1988 June (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Colloquium (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Faculty records (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Financial records (Box-folder 23: 8)
  - Memoranda
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 9)
    - 1947-1958 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Messages (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Minutes of meetings
    - 1948 April (Box-folder 23: 12)
    - 1956 April-December (Box-folder 23: 13)
    - 1957 January-November (Box-folder 23: 14)
    - 1958 January-May (Box-folder 23: 15)
    - 1963 August (Box-folder 23: 16)
  - Newsletters (Box-folder 23: 17)
  - Order of worship (Box-folder 23: 18)
  - News releases (Box-folder 23: 19)
  - Printed matter (Box-folder 23: 20)
  - Program (Box-folder 23: 21)
  - Proposals (Box-folder 23: 22)
  - Reports
    - Undated (Box-folder 23: 23)
    - 1954 July (Box-folder 23: 24)
    - 1956 January (Box-folder 23: 25)
    - 1959 March (Box-folder 23: 26)
  - Retirement benefits program (Box-folder 23: 27)
  - Schedule (Box-folder 23: 28)
  - Subject file
    - Conferences and seminars
      Held at Stanford University unless otherwise stated.
      - A Conference - Planning Workshop, 1959 (Box-folder 24: 1)
      - Conference on the Social Sciences, Hoover Institution, Stanford University, 1957 (Box-folder 24: 2)
      - Fulbright Conference on American Studies, Cambridge, Great Britain, 1954
        - General (Box-folder 24: 3)
        - Bibliography and suggested reading list (Box-folder 24: 4)
        - Correspondence (Box-folder 24: 5)
        - Notes (Box-folder 24: 6)
        - Press releases (Box-folder 24: 7)
        - Program (Box-folder 24: 8)
        - Telegrams (Box-folder 24: 9)
        - Miscellany (Box-folder 24: 10)
      - Institute of International Relations Conference, Asilomar and Stanford University
        - General (Box-folder 24: 11)
        - Correspondence, 1947-1959 (Box-folder 24: 12-15)
        - List of participants (Box-folder 24: 16)
        - Memoranda, 1958 (Box-folder 24: 17)
        - News releases (Box-folder 24: 18)
        - Outlines (Box-folder 24: 19)
        - Pamphlets (Box-folder 24: 20)
        - Program (Box-folder 24: 21)
        - Report, 1958 (Box-folder 24: 22)
        - Schedule (Box-folder 24: 23)
        - Speech (Box-folder 24: 24)
        - Telegrams (Box-folder 24: 25)
      - Russian and the Development of International Relations (RADIR) Project
        - General (Box-folder 24: 26)
        - Memoranda (Box-folder 24: 27)
        - Notes (Box-folder 24: 28)
        - Research summary (Box-folder 24: 29)
        - Statements (Box-folder 24: 30)
        - Workbook (Box-folder 24: 31)
        - Workbook (Box-folder 25: 1)
      - Soviet Impact on International Relations, Hoover Institution, Stanford University
        - General (Box-folder 25: 2)
        - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 25: 3)
        - Discussion materials (Box-folder 25: 4)
        - Memoranda, 1948 (Box-folder 25: 5)
        - Notes (Box-folder 25: 6)
        - Outlines (Box-folder 25: 7)
        - Schedule (Box-folder 25: 8)
        - Telegrams (Box-folder 25: 9)
      - Western College Congress and Pacific Northwest College Congress
        - General (Box-folder 25: 10)
        - Address, delivered by Ralph J. Bunche, 1951 (Box-folder 25: 11)
        - Bulletins (Box-folder 25: 12)
        - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 25: 13)
        - Financial records (Box-folder 25: 14)
        - Memoranda, 1947 (Box-folder 25: 15)
        - Minutes of meetings, 1947 (Box-folder 25: 16)
        - Notes (Box-folder 25: 17)
        - Press releases (Box-folder 25: 18)
        - Program (Box-folder 25: 19)
        - Reports, 1947 (Box-folder 25: 20)
        - Telegrams (Box-folder 25: 21)
    - Courses of instruction
      - General (Box-folder 26: 1)
      - History
        - American Diplomatic History (Box-folder 26: 2)
        - History of Medieval Europe (Box-folder 26: 3)
        - History of Modern Europe
          - Congress of Vienna (Box-folder 26: 4)
          - French Revolution and Napoleon (Box-folder 26: 5)
        - History of the Nineteenth Century (Box-folder 26: 6)
        - History of Western Civilization (Box-folder 26: 7)
      - International relations
        - General (Box-folder 26: 8)
        - International Studies Seminar (Box-folder 26: 9-10)
        - International Studies Seminar (Box-folder 27: 1)
        - Problems of Peace Making (Box-folder 27: 2)
        - Social Forces and World Politics (Box-folder 27: 3)
        - United States Interests in European Security (Box-folder 27: 4)
      - Pacific-Asiatic-Russian studies
        - Brochure (Box-folder 27: 5)
        - Committee on Pacific and Asiatic Studies (Box-folder 27: 6)
        - List of courses (Box-folder 27: 7)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - Travel
      - General (Box-folder 27: 9)
      - Airline schedule (Box-folder 27: 10)